# Muhammadali Nurmuhammedov

 ♦ Tashkent, Uzbekistan
 □ topcoder.n@gmail.com
 • +998 97 828 09 69
 in nurmuhammedov

**O** nurmuhammedov

# Middle Frontend Developer

I have been actively working in web development since 10/2021 (3+ years of experience), successfully completing 10+ real projects (large/medium). I am currently looking for an experienced team to enhance my technical skills and participate in complex projects with a large number of users. I would be delighted to join your team and contribute to its success

# Experience

## Frontend developer

Technocorp - technocorp.uz ☑

Tashkent, Uzbekistan Dec 2022 - Present

- Technocorp is a software development IT company that primarily works on government projects. The company specializes in developing CRM, LMS, ERP, E-commerce platforms, websites, and internal information systems.
- At Technocorp, I gained strong experience developing projects using react.js, next.js, typescript, state
  management, utility react libraries, unit testing, ui libraries, websocket, SEO, analyzing and understanding
  existing projects code and so on. Additionally, I learned backend technologies such as node.js, express.js.
  This experience has allowed me to build strong technical skills in Frontend development.

### Frontend Developer Intern

Tashkent, Uzbekistan Jun 2022 - Nov 2022

During my internship, I gained strong experience in working with REST APIs and managing file structures.

### Freelance Frontend Developer

 $Self ext{-}Employed$ 

Tashkent, Uzbekistan Oct 2021 – May 2022

During my freelance work, I developed strong theoretical knowledge in javascript (ES6+), react.js and I
gained strong experience in solving practical problems using programming languages like javascript and
typescript.

### Education

### Tashkent University of Information Technologies

Tashkent, Uzbekistan

Oct 2020 - Oct 2024

∘ Bachelor's degree: Software Engineering 🗹

∘ **GPA:** 4.03/5 🗹

∘ University website: tuit.uz 🗹

# Personal Development Process

Tashkent, Uzbekistan

Apr 2021 - Sep 2021

Course: Frontend development 

Academy website: pdp.uz

## **Projects**

### Raqamli nazorat

itc.gis.uz

• This information system was developed for the **Uzkomnazorat Inspection** (**O'zkomnazorat**). This system monitors government organizations' websites and information systems.

### Davlat-xususiy sherikchilik AT

• This information system for the **Ministry of Water Resources** that automates the process of transferring water management facilities to private partnership management.

### Ishonch

ishonch.technocorp.uz ☑ ishonch-hpx.iiv.uz ☑

• This information system was developed for the **Ministry of Internal Affairs**. This system automates the process of **call center** (short number "1286") ishonch-hpx.iiv.uz **Z** - operates in a local network.

E-Kinolog.iiv.uz ☑

o This information system for maintaining the registry of cynologists for the **Ministry of Internal Affairs** (e-kinolog.iiv.uz 

✓ - operates in a local network).

### Other projects

- ∘ Information systems: suv.technocorp.uz 🗹, avtoyulnorma.uz 🗹, avtoyulilm.uz 🗹, pmtests.uz 🗹
- ∘ Websites: artelcarts.com 🗹, uzavtoyul.uz 🗹, uzkomnazorat.uz 🗹, fmi-platforma.uz 🗹

# Skills

Languages: Uzbek - Native, Russian and English - B2 (proficient in listening and reading)

Programing languages: JavaScript, TypeScript

**Technologies:** HTML5, CSS3, CSS preprocessors (SASS, SCSS), React Js, Next Js, State Management (Redux, Redux Toolkit), Experience with UI Libraries (Material UI, Chakra UI, Prime React), Strong experience with REST APIs, Strong experience with Websocket, GraphQL, Unit Testing (Jest, React Testing), 10+ utility react libraries, Node.js, Express.js